{
    "subject": "resource/Alfara_de_la_Baronia",
    "predicate": "property/subdivisionType",
    "object": "resource/Comarcas_of_Spain",
    "human_readable": "Alfara de la Baronia is a type of Comarcas of Spain.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8109154105186462,
            "question": "Where is Alfara de la Baronia located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7982470989227295,
            "question": "What type of geographic region is Alfara de la Baronia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7558869123458862,
            "question": "Does Alfara de la Baronia belong to a specific country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6704143285751343,
            "question": "What are some interesting facts about Alfara de la Baronia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6633445024490356,
            "question": "Are there any notable landmarks or features associated with Alfara de la Baronia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.654890775680542,
            "question": "What is the history of Alfara de la Baronia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6069978475570679,
            "question": "Can you name other examples of Comarcas in Spain?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5930378437042236,
            "question": "How would you describe the culture of Alfara de la Baronia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5666583180427551,
            "question": "What are Comarcas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48283177614212036,
            "question": "Are there any festivals or events celebrated in Alfara de la Baronia?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Alfara de la Baronia is a type of Comarcas of Spain.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4294_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are Comarcas?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4294_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How would you describe the culture of Alfara de la Baronia?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4294_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name other examples of Comarcas in Spain?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4294_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4294_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4294_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4294_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4294_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4294_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4294_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4294_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4294_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4294_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4294_6.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents do not contain any information that suggests Alfara de la Baronia is a comarca (a traditional administrative division) of Spain. The documents primarily provide geographical, demographic, and locational details about Alfara de la Baronia but do not mention its classification as a comarca."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Alfara de la Baronia is not a type of Comarcas (administrative divisions) of Spain, but rather a municipality within the Valencia Province.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided context describes Alfara de la Baronia as a municipality located within the Valencia Province of Spain. It mentions details about its population, geographical location, and even hiking trails in the area. There's no information suggesting it's a type of Comarcas.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information consistently refers to Alfara de la Baronia as a municipality or town, not as a type of Comarcas of Spain.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information describes Alfara de la Baronia as a municipality within the Valencia province, Valencian Community, Spain. It does not mention Alfara de la Baronia being a Comarca (a type of administrative division in Spain), thus indicating that the statement is incorrect.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}